<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bio Lab</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bio Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&#xA;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 1</title>
      <link>/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.&#xA;Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alice Smith</title>
      <link>/team/alice-smith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/alice-smith/</guid>
      <description>Alice leads the lab and has extensive experience in cryo-EM and structural virology. Her research focuses on understanding virus structure and developing new methods for cryo-EM data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Johnson</title>
      <link>/team/bob-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/bob-johnson/</guid>
      <description>Bob is a Postdoctoral Researcher focusing on analyzing cryo-EM data and refining structural models. He is particularly interested in developing new algorithms for image processing and 3D reconstruction. Bob enjoys hiking and exploring national parks in his free time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carol Williams</title>
      <link>/team/carol-williams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/carol-williams/</guid>
      <description>Carol is a graduate student investigating the conformational dynamics of viral proteins.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Brown</title>
      <link>/team/david-brown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/team/david-brown/</guid>
      <description>David helps with sample preparation and data acquisition.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Processing</title>
      <link>/protocols/image-processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/protocols/image-processing/</guid>
      <description>Steps for processing cryo-EM images.&#xA;Import micrographs into RELION. Perform motion correction. Estimate CTF parameters. Pick particles and generate initial model. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Preparation</title>
      <link>/protocols/sample-prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/protocols/sample-prep/</guid>
      <description>This protocol describes the steps for preparing cryo-EM samples.&#xA;Grow cells to mid-log phase. Harvest and wash with buffer. Apply sample to grids and plunge freeze. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
